Madam,
my name is Venugopal Rao.
I [clears throat] recently
heard about a product called Elevent from ICCL Hamba, which is being marketed very
aggressively
.
I have come to tell you some benefits about this policy called Elevate, which you
will receive today. If you are an
elevator owner, you are 100%
correct. Elevate is really
changing the market very well because
its features are like that. Sir, it is
correctly named Elevate, which is
really a highlight. If there is a product,
you can tell me. So what else is there, if we
come to age before 80, that is,
from 18 years to 125 years, we can
give the policy to the customer.  So,
we will consider a policy for children up to 30 years old
.  So apart from that, if the 10
comes out, not just for one year, but for five
years, the customer can also keep the policy by making a continuous
payment at the same time.
Like when we buy any product, we
buy a bigger item because we think that the discount will be better if we buy a bigger one than if we buy a smaller one. Similarly, when it
comes to a health policy, if you
pay for five years, you will have
six premiums, depending on your age and vice versa. So if you do it for one year, if you do it for two years, you will have a 10% premium discount
.  If you take it for three years, you get a 30%
15% discount.  The fourth year is also
15, the fifth year is also 15, and
customers who have taken long 10 will have a good profit
.  Apart from that,
we also offer a nice CIBIL discount.  So
this is a 15% discount, if you are a civil servant,
up to 15% discount and but more over this
long tenue, up to 15%, up to 30%
discount for customers, it is very
useful.  For long tenure, there
is also the option of jump start.  So, if
customers take medicines regularly for any disease like BP, sugar, etc., then they have
to take medicines for BP, cholesterol, obesity, etc., which normally have a
waiting period of three years.
But if we jump start it, we
will consider three years to be 30 days, and the waiting
period will be reduced.  Okay,
so after 30 days, the customer will no longer need it, and there
will be an option called Power Booster.  So
I'm saying all these are advances, but when it comes to heroic
features, like the power booster,
you get a policy with a customer premium of 10 lakhs.
Next Power Bister will
add another 10 locks for the next year. Sir, your
coverage is
okay.
So if you take it continuously for 10 years,
your coverage will be 10, 10, 10,
100%,
100%, up to the said one crore rupees, no matter what it does or does not do. There are no conditions for it.  It keeps
growing unlimitedly, 10 100%, and then you
put infinite care in it.
Madam,
infinite care
means infinity, right? Sir, there is
no real limit to it.  Okay, so what
that means is that if it has turned off its customer, at
any time during the policy year, the
customer can now claim a 10-
lock policy or a 30-lock policy
.  But now, suppose a
critical illness, major accident,
medical bill comes and it is more than your coverage. Let's say the
customer gets Rs 1 crore instead of 30 locks
because inflation
increases. Medical bills are also
increasing a lot. So in the future,
whatever the customer gets, there is
no limit to it.
So, no matter how much the
customer gets billed, we
will pay it. So, it is the customer's choice. So,
we do not have any conditions on it.
When the customer comes, then the
customer can train it once in the policy year. There is an
option called Internet Care. So, when it
comes, I
said in Power Goose, I
said Jumpstart, I said Internet, so
also, it will have unlimited sum in shot. The
customer
can turn off unlimited sum in shot. There is
also a fee. There is
OPD facility, it comes up to Rs 5000
.  This includes
coverage up to and including a root canal
.  So our OPD facility
is in an elevated state.  There is also a maternity
option [to have a throat transplant] with a two-year waiting period.
This includes worldwide coverage and
you will not have any caps.
Sir, normally, if you want a single private room with
worldwide coverage, how much amount should you
take? Madam, even
if you take 25 lakhs above, you will
also take the add-on worldwide coverage
.
So if you take it worldwide, it means that after two years of
marriage, worldwide coverage will also
come.  How much can a family
take, madam? This is the maximum limit.
This is a family policy.
We can take a policy for two adults and three kids. What's
more, there
is an unlimited reset. No matter
how many times you claim,
we will give you as many claims as you want. [Clearing throat] That means that if any of
these five members are
hospitalized, the
coverage will
be reset again within 24 hours.  So that's a very good benefit,
we can say that apart from that in Elevate, I
told you about the coverage. Another thing is that you have
health insurance so far, you have pre and
post hospitalization, right? It's 90
and 180 days. Free is 90
days post and then you have 180 days of coverage
.  Apart from that, when it comes to health insurance, there is a question of
when it can be used.   It's not that
I can get any checkup or medical test done normally, but if I have to
be hospitalized after doing it, I mean, up until now, it was 24
hours, but it would
n't have been claimed, but we have also started two-hour hospitalization in Elevate
.  So, if the customer has any day care
procedures, Ayush treatment, or anything else, their
BP fluctuates. Sometimes, the
customer doesn't know about it, but if their
BP suddenly becomes
high when they have nothing to do, or if they have any other underlying condition, if they
go to the hospital, the doctor will say that they need to inject a sedative,
then they will obviously
admit them to inject a sedative.  After admission, the
customer has to stay for four to five hours.
After observation, the customer will tell you when you can
leave and send you away. So
even in that case, we offer cashless payment, which
covers two hours of hospitalization.  Also, you have
an option called Durable Medical Equipment,
which will
also be inducted in the coming days, starting from the 15th. So, if
they need any equipment, like a green chair or any other accident,
we also cover medical equipment in the policy. The
ward called Plane
Protector is a mandatory item that the
customer must take because
it is a consumable item, and any non-consumable
item will be covered, like
PEP kit, syringe, gloves, etc. All
these items will not be covered.  So if we
take the Client Protector option, it will
be 100% cashless.
And more over,
we don't have cashless anywhere.  NV Cash
means that it may or
may not be in a panel at a time.
Our customers keep asking whether a hospital is a network hospital or not.
Even without working with a network hospital, if a
customer has any plant surgeries, they say, "I do
n't have the network in this hospital, but
I want it here because some
doctors give me the same treatment as these doctors."
He means, "I have a
sentiment." So in such a condition, if the customer calls the customer
care 24 hours before or 48 hours before and
intimates, we can avail cashless there too.
So
along with these, we also provide I-Take Care
.  So, we provide 24/7 unlimited telemedical
services, video calls, and chat
calls, so that the customer
can connect with the doctor.
That year and so far
we have been told that the doctor will be unavailable for 24/7,
thank you, madam.